Hello friends, ICICI Pidency Life
Insurance Company Limited has announced its
fourth quarter numbers ending on March 31.
So let's
see.  Let us first know what has been
announced in the board meeting.
Here the company has announced final dividend of ₹1.65 per equity share.
And
regarding this, the record date has
not been announced yet.  So here you have it, the
figures for the company's consolidated financial results for the quarter ended March 31, 2026, are
given here at the end.  First of all, let us talk about the
total income earned by the company
in this quarter, which is ₹3782 crores.  In the
December quarter, the profit
was ₹22,302 crore and in the
quarter of last year, the profit was ₹15,637
crore.  A big decline is being seen in the total income here.
If we talk about total income year on year, then a
decline of 76% is being seen here.   The
total income of the company has decreased by 76%.   At
the same time, if you
talk about it quarter on quarter and compare it with the December quarter, then there
is an even bigger decline here.  Here a decline of 83% is
visible in it.  And
you can see that the main reason for the decline here is the
company's income from investment,
here a huge loss is being shown in it.
A huge loss of ₹16,302 crore is being
shown here for the March quarter.  Which
is the section of Income from Investment.  And along with this,
if we talk about the net
premium income of the company, you can see that there is an
increase there.
In the previous year's quarter it was
₹16,300
₹16,369 crore.  This year it has increased to
₹1,180
crore.  So, there is an increase in the net premium income of the company
and there is an even bigger jump in it quarter on quarter.
Here it has increased from ₹1,809 crore to
₹1,180
crore.  So the decline in total income is due to
loss from
investment and income from
investment.
Let us now see what the total
expenses are.
This is for ₹2150 crore for the March quarter.   In the
December quarter, it was worth
₹2333 crore and in the previous year's
quarter, it was worth ₹1343 crore.
So the company's expenses have also
reduced significantly.  Expenses have been
managed well.  There has been a considerable decline.
Let us now see what the profit for the
period has been.  This is profit
for the period and after tax and
extra and extraordinary items.
This is Rs 623 crore 91 lakh of the company.  Approximately
₹624 crore.  The profit in the December quarter
was ₹387 crore 15 lakh and in the
March quarter of last year, the profit was
₹385 crore 28 lakh.  So
due to reduction in expenses, there has been
no decline in the profits of the company.  An
increase in profit is being seen.
Year on year profit has increased from ₹385 crore to
₹623 crore.
Quarter on quarter, it has also increased from ₹387 crore to
₹623 crore.  Let's talk about the
earnings per share, this is
for the March quarter at ₹4.31 per share.  Whereas
in the December quarter the share was at ₹2.68 and in the
March quarter of last year the
share was at ₹2.67.  So
friends, this was the information in the video of March ending quarterly numbers of Prudential ICI ICICI Pashul Life
Insurance Company Limited. That's all for
now. I hope
you liked the video. If you liked the
video, then like it and
subscribe to the channel. Thank you.